TheaterWorks Records MS023
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
TheaterWorks Records
1978 -- 1989
1972 -- 2010
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
TheaterWorks
MS023
12.3 Linear Feet
5 Audiovisual Object(s)
Arrangement
The collection is organized into nine series: Productions and Shows, Photographs, Collaborative Projects, Administrative files and Correspondence, Biographical Information, Financial Information, Fundraising and Grants, Publicity and Media, A/V Media.
Scope and Contents
The TheaterWorks Collection includes production notes, scripts, notes from collaborative projects, publicity (including original posters and programs), financial records, general administrative records, resumes and headshots, photographs and slides, sound and video recordings, grant materials, fundraising and subscriber information. The bulk of the material dates from 1978 to 1989 and documents the many shows and projects TheaterWorks created and participated in as well as the artists and theater groups with whom they collaborated.
This collection contains examples of the fundraising and grant writing work necessary for a small theater company, and the kinds of financial records it generates. Additionally, there are some original scripts with accompanying production notes that might be of interest to new experimental or student theater companies.
Biographical / Historical
TheaterWorks, an experimental theater company in Boston, was founded in 1980 and performed between 1981-1989. The company grew out of Reality Theater, another small experimental company that produced works in the late 1970s. TheaterWorks used small theater settings to introduce Boston audiences to innovative productions and produced new and original works.
The company performed at several locations around the city including a space at UMass Boston downtown and at Suffolk University. The company won multiple regional awards including "best new company," "best individual performance," and "best play" as well as critical recognition for their work. People who were artistically instrumental in the company include the co-founding Artistic Directors Vincent Murphy and Tim McDonough, both of whom acted, directed and wrote for TheaterWorks. The later Artistic Directors David Miller and Downing Cless and playwright-in-residence Jon Lipsky also had significant influence in shaping and maintaining the company.
This collection is connected to Tufts University in several ways: TheaterWorks occasionally performed in a space on-campus, Vincent Murphy was the Head of the Acting/Directing Program (1985-1986), and Downing Cless is a Tufts faculty member.
TheaterWorks stopped producing works in 1989 for artistic, financial and personnel reasons. The founders continue to be actively involved in both academic and regional theater.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
TheaterWorks (Boston); Experimental theater -- Massachusetts -- Boston -- Sources; Greater Boston arts
- Productions and shows, 1973 -- 1990; MS023.001; 2.4 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains flyers, programs, script and production development notes, schedules, and drafts of scripts. The material is spread evenly across the included dates. These records are a direct result of the realized productions of Reality Theater and TheaterWorks. Each show file contains different types and amounts of information on each production.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  75 years from the date of creation. Open for research.
  - Beginner's Luck [Reality Theater], 1978; MS023.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Open for research.
  - Enough [Reality Theater], 1979; MS023.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Billy the kid [Reality Theater], 1978; MS023.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Curse of the starving class [Reality Theater], 1978 -- 1980; MS023.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Master of Ecstasy [Reality Theater], 1978 -- 1980; MS023.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Orestia [Reality Theater], 1977; MS023.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Outside the door [Reality Theater], 1975; MS023.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Reality Theater, 1973; MS023.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Reality theater, 1978; MS023.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Hamlet, 1979 -- 1981; MS023.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Hamlet budget, 1979 -- 1981; MS023.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Hamlet script, 1979 -- 1981; MS023.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Hamlet film, 1982; MS023.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Hamlet film/video - Tim Hill, 1982; MS023.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Hamlet film/video - Fanlight, 1981; MS023.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Me and my shadow, 1981 -- 1983; MS023.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Tongues, 1979; MS023.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Tongues- royalties, 1981; MS023.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Tongues promotion, 1981; MS023.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Tongues scripts, 1981; MS023.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Murder now, 1983; MS023.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Murder now, 1983; MS023.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Split britches - beast, 1982; MS023.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Stallers farm, 1982; MS023.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Stallers farm, 1982; MS023.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Living in exile, 1982; MS023.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Living in exile, 1982; MS023.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Exile, 1982; MS023.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Late night series, 1983 -- 1984; MS023.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Simplicissimus, 1982; MS023.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Pathways script, 1981; MS023.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Pathways to madness - general, 1985; MS023.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Pathways, 1982; MS023.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Pathways, 1982; MS023.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Pathways - wilson script, 1982; MS023.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Out out, 1983; MS023.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Out out, 1983; MS023.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Happy ending, 1983 -- 1984; MS023.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Scheherazade's sister, 1983 -- 1984; MS023.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Scheherazade's sister, 1983 -- 1984; MS023.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Scheherazade's sister, 1983 -- 1984; MS023.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Coming through slaughter, 1982 -- 1983; MS023.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Coming through slaughter script, 1983; MS023.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - Lear, 1984; MS023.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - King Lear, 1984; MS023.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - Equity - King Lear, 1984; MS023.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - Shrew, 1984; MS023.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Taming of the Shrew, 1984; MS023.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Equity - Taming of the Shrew, 1984; MS023.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Bundle, 1984; MS023.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Bundle, 1984; MS023.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Fo/Country/Family Album, 1985; MS023.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Enough, 1985; MS023.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Bongo Bongo: Bongo Bongo, 1985; MS023.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Bongo Bongo: Bongo Bongo [press clippings], 1985; MS023.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - The Island, 1986; MS023.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Barriers, 1986; MS023.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Make it like the Movies, 1986; MS023.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Make it like the Movies [master script (Aug)], 1986; MS023.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Make it like the Movies [script], 1986; MS023.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Targeted City, 1986; MS023.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Targeted City, 1986; MS023.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - [Ballard Theater-In the Traffic of a Targeted City], 1986; MS023.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Mensch Meier, 1987; MS023.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - [Mensch Meier], 1987; MS023.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - [Kasper], 1987; MS023.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Kasper, 1987; MS023.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Baby Steps, 1988; MS023.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Baby Steps, 1988; MS023.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - [Sold Out], 1987 -- 1988; MS023.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Sold Out script, 1988; MS023.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - [TWIP], 1988; MS023.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Works in progress, 1988; MS023.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Idol Cooking, 1988; MS023.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - The Complete Guide to Idol Cooking, 1988; MS023.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - [Anarchist], 1988; MS023.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Anarchist... May, 1988; MS023.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - [Anarchist], 1988; MS023.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Bad Water, 1988; MS023.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Dinos-promo, 1989; MS023.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - [Dino Development], 1989; MS023.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - [Dinosaurs 1990-Version 1 28 Dec 1988], 1988 -- 1990; MS023.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - [Dino research], 1988 -- 1990; MS023.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - TWIP, 1989; MS023.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - Bad Water/Dream Kitchen, 1989; MS023.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Black Witness, 1989; MS023.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
- Photographs, 1979 -- 1990; MS023.002; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains photographs, contact sheets, negatives and slides. The photos are spread over the inclusive dates. The images include production photos, publicity pictures and candid photos of actors during the rehearsal process. On many photos credit is given to the photographer and the people in a picture are named on the back.
  This series is arranged chronologically
  - R.T. Photos [includes Enough], 1979 -- 1985; MS023.002.003.00001 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Photos, 1980 -- 1982; MS023.002.003.00002 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - [SHAGW/Boston (?)], 1980 -- 1990; MS023.002.003.00003 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - [Photographs - TheatreWorks PO CDC w/31], 1980 -- 1990; MS023.002.003.00004 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - [TheatreWorks PO CCD F/21], 1980 -- 1990; MS023.002.003.00005 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Slaughter photos, 1983; MS023.002.003.00006 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Photos, 1982 -- 1984; MS023.002.003.00007 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Photos, 1984 -- 1986; MS023.002.003.00008 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Photos, 1986 -- 1988; MS023.002.003.00009 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Photos, 1988; MS023.002.003.00010 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Photograph of David Miller in Out Out, 1983; MS023.000446 (Box MS023 Shared 3, Folder 15)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Gift of David Miller, 2021, accession MS-2021-048.
- Collaborative projects, 1974 -- 1990; MS023.003; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains meeting notes, production design sketches, contracts, publicity and correspondense. The records are spread out over the inclusive dates. All of these records were created as results of collaborative efforts between TheaterWorks and other theater groups and range from performances to regional artistic alliances.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Arts Boston, 1987; MS023.003.003.00011 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - BB and K Communications, 1980 -- 1990; MS023.003.003.00012 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Bread and Puppet, 1980 -- 1990; MS023.003.003.00013 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - BRTA, 1987; MS023.003.003.00014 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - BRTA, 1987; MS023.003.003.00015 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - BRTA, 1987; MS023.003.003.00016 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Boston Theatre of the Deaf, 1980 -- 1990; MS023.003.003.00017 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Chaikin and Theatre Artists, 1987; MS023.003.003.00018 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Collaborators [Julie Taymor], 1983 -- 1984; MS023.003.003.00019 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Crosswalks Thea., 1982; MS023.003.003.00020 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - ICA, 1983; MS023.003.003.00021 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Idaho, 1984; MS023.003.003.00022 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Idaho Shakes, 1984; MS023.003.003.00023 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Late Night, 1980 -- 1990; MS023.003.003.00024 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Medicine, 1974; MS023.003.003.00025 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - New Theatre Associates, 1980; MS023.003.003.00026 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Spokesong, 1986; MS023.003.003.00027 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Squat, 1984; MS023.003.003.00028 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Squat Theater, 1983; MS023.003.003.00029 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Squat Theater, 1985; MS023.003.003.00030 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
  - Mass Com/Squat fiasco, 1984; MS023.003.003.00031 (Box MS023 Shared 1)
- Administrative files and correspondence, 1973 -- 1998; 1979 -- 1989; MS023.004; 1.7 Linear Feet
  This series contains awards, season listings, organization bylaws, organizational background and their mission statement, blank forms, meeting minutes, contracts, job descriptions, notes on searches for a performance space, insurance, production note cards and a few mac floppy disks. The bulk of the information is from 1979-1989. These records were created in everyday business and relate to multiple shows or seasons.
  This series is arranged alphabetically, with an attempt to also group topically.
  - 1981 Awards, MS023.004.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - 1982-83 Awards, 1982 -- 1983; MS023.004.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - [Admin Files season], 1980 -- 1981; MS023.004.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - [Admin Files season], 1984 -- 1985; MS023.004.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - [Admin Files TW] 1 of 2, 1987 -- 1988; MS023.004.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - [Admin Files TW] 2 of 2, 1987 -- 1988; MS023.004.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - 1983-84 season, 1983 -- 1984; MS023.004.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - 1985-86 season, 1985 -- 1986; MS023.004.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - 1986-87 season, 1986 -- 1987; MS023.004.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - 1987-88 season, 1987 -- 1988; MS023.004.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Articles of the orgazinization, bylaws, 1982; MS023.004.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - [Admin Files Background of TheaterWorks], 1982; MS023.004.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Bernstein Project, 1984; MS023.004.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Blank forms, 1980 -- 1990; MS023.004.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Blank C. Card reservations, 1980 -- 1990; MS023.004.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Blank salary receipts, 1980 -- 1990; MS023.004.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - TW Board, 1980 -- 1990; MS023.004.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Minutes Board, 1981 -- 1984; MS023.004.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Board of Directors, 1983; MS023.004.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - TW Board, 1983; MS023.004.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Board, 1984; MS023.004.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Box office statements, 1980 -- 1990; MS023.004.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - [Budgets], 1983; MS023.004.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - OOBA contact sheet, 1982; MS023.004.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Contracts, 1979 -- 1982; MS023.004.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - 1987-88 Contracts, 1987 -- 1988; MS023.004.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Hasty contract, 1983; MS023.004.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - 3-5 Yr Artistic and Mgt Plan (Louise Stevens) Office manager duties, 1982; MS023.004.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - [Contract-sample equity], 1987; MS023.004.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Archives search [Correspondence], 1998; MS023.004.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - A.R.T. [Correspondence], 1981; MS023.004.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - From the audience [Correspondence], 1980 -- 1983; MS023.004.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Brattle, J.D. [Correspondence], 1982; MS023.004.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Chester Atkins [Correspondence], 1983; MS023.004.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Corresp. to Globe [Correspondence], 1983; MS023.004.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - Legal [Correspondence], 1982 -- 1983; MS023.004.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - International Theater Institute [Correspondence], 1982 -- 1983; MS023.004.004.00037 (Box 4)
  - Political Letters [Correspondence], 1987 -- 1989; MS023.004.004.00038 (Box 4)
  - Corresp. with Vinnie [Correspondence], 1986; MS023.004.004.00039 (Box 4)
  - VIP Letters [Correspondence], 1981 -- 1990; MS023.004.004.00040 (Box 4)
  - Development events, 1984; MS023.004.004.00041 (Box 4)
  - Guidelines to fundraising and donors, 1983; MS023.004.004.00042 (Box 4)
  - Insurance, 1983; MS023.004.004.00043 (Box 4)
  - Insurance, 1983; MS023.004.004.00044 (Box 4)
  - Insurance, 1982; MS023.004.004.00045 (Box 4)
  - Workers comp, 1983; MS023.004.004.00046 (Box 4)
  - Job descriptions, 1982; MS023.004.004.00047 (Box 4)
  - Job descriptions, 1982; MS023.004.004.00048 (Box 4)
  - Northeastern, 1982; MS023.004.004.00049 (Box 4)
  - ISF and company meeting, 1986; MS023.004.004.00050 (Box 4)
  - Meeting minutes, 1987; MS023.004.004.00051 (Box 4)
  - Board [Admin files misc], 1983; MS023.004.004.00052 (Box 4)
  - [Mission statement], 1980 -- 1983; MS023.004.004.00053 (Box 4)
  - [Admin files-notebook], 1988; MS023.004.004.00054 (Box 4)
  - [Admin files-personal publicity], 1983; MS023.004.004.00055 (Box 4)
  - [Admin files-personal misc], 1982 -- 1986; MS023.004.004.00056 (Box 4)
  - [Admin files-presentation handouts], 1988; MS023.004.004.00057 (Box 4)
  - TW [Admin files-process and philosophy], 1984; MS023.004.004.00058 (Box 4)
  - Promotion-Bio's, 1982; MS023.004.004.00059 (Box 4)
  - Rights/royalties, 1983; MS023.004.004.00060 (Box 4)
  - Season info, 1984 -- 1986; MS023.004.004.00061 (Box 4)
  - Shadow, 1981 -- 1982; MS023.004.004.00062 (Box 4)
  - [Admin files-sources of funds], 1982 -- 1983; MS023.004.004.00063 (Box 4)
  - Space search, 1983 -- 1984; MS023.004.005.00001 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Space-correspondence, 1983; MS023.004.005.00002 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Space-insurance, 1984; MS023.004.005.00003 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Space-U. Mass/Boston, 1981 -- 1983; MS023.004.005.00004 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - U. Mass space proposal, 1982; MS023.004.005.00005 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - [Admin files-space, Suffolk], 1985; MS023.004.005.00006 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Space, 1983 -- 1984; MS023.004.005.00007 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Suffolk $ and shows, 1984; MS023.004.005.00008 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - [Admin files-space info], 1984; MS023.004.005.00009 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Staff, 1982 -- 1983; MS023.004.005.00010 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Staff-minutes of meetings, 1983; MS023.004.005.00011 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Subscribers, 1983 -- 1984; MS023.004.005.00012 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - [Admin files-technical assistance Stacy Eddy], 1986; MS023.004.005.00013 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Telephone, 1982 -- 1983; MS023.004.005.00014 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - [Admin files-TW misc.], 1982; MS023.004.005.00015 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - TheaterWorks, 1978; MS023.004.005.00016 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - TheaterWorks misc., 1988; MS023.004.005.00017 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Enough [admin files], 1983; MS023.004.005.00018 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - TheaterWorks, 1973; MS023.004.005.00019 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - TheaterWorks misc [admin files], 1986; MS023.004.005.00020 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - [Admin file-misc], 1980 -- 1981; MS023.004.005.00021 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - TW misc, 1985; MS023.004.005.00022 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - TW misc, 1985 -- 1986; MS023.004.005.00023 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - [Admin files-misc publicity], 1985 -- 1986; MS023.004.005.00024 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Misc-1988-89 (and earlier), 1980 -- 1989; MS023.004.005.00025 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - [Admin files-misc. originals, 1983; MS023.004.005.00026 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Tufts, 1984 -- 1985; MS023.004.005.00027 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Ushers, 1980 -- 1990; MS023.004.005.00028 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
    .
  - Video, 1984; MS023.004.005.00029 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Volunteer, 1980 -- 1990; MS023.004.005.00030 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Production file (1 of 2), 1980 -- 1990; MS023.004.005.00031 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Production file (2 of 2), 1980 -- 1990; MS023.004.005.00032 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Macintosh computer disks, 1980 -- 1990; MS023.004.005.00033 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
- Biographical information, 1972 -- 1990; MS023.005; 0.75 Linear Feet
  This series contains biographical excerpts suitable for program notes, headshots, resumes and Vinny Murphy's personal papers and projects. The records are spread across the 1980s and contain small amounts of biographical information (suitable for publicity or promotion) on artists who were part of, or auditioned for TheaterWorks.
  - [Biographical-assorted], 1986; MS023.005.005.00034 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Tenkei Gekijyo, 1981; MS023.005.005.00035 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Staff-Hankins, Rose, 1982 -- 1983; MS023.005.005.00036 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - [Biographic-headshots], 1984 -- 1989; MS023.005.005.00037 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Incentive resumes, 1980 -- 1990; MS023.005.005.00038 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Murphy, Vincent [Personal], 1972 -- 1987; MS023.005.005.00039 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - NY show [Paleologos, Nicholas], 1984; MS023.005.005.00040 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Bios [Assorted resumes], 1980 -- 1990; MS023.005.005.00041 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - [Resumes], 1980 -- 1990; MS023.005.005.00042 (Box MS023 Shared 2)
  - Farewell cards, 1989; MS023.005.015.00001 (Box Shared 126)
- Financial information, 1980 -- 1993; MS023.006; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains annual reports, financial statements from different fiscal years, bank receipts and statements, budgets, a business plan, receipts, and IRS information including exemption forms, federal and state returns and 990 forms. The records were created throughout the inclusive dates. This is the financial paperwork generated by any small non-profit organization and is an excellent look at the kinds of record keeping and financial exercises necessary for producing small, independent theater.
  - Accts. payable, 1983 -- 1984; MS023.006.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Arts Boston, 1983; MS023.006.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Audit accounting, 1983; MS023.006.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - [Annual report-Globe foundation support], 1986 -- 1987; MS023.006.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - [Financial balance sheet], 1984; MS023.006.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Bank, 1985 -- 1986; MS023.006.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Bank of Boston-statements, 1983; MS023.006.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Bank of Boston-statements, 1983 -- 1984; MS023.006.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Bank of Boston and Key Bank, 1988; MS023.006.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - [Budget], 1985; MS023.006.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - [Business plan], 1980 -- 1990; MS023.006.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - [CD and CR Summaries], 1984; MS023.006.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - [CD's], 1983 -- 1984; MS023.006.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - CPA file, 1985; MS023.006.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - [Daily sales reports], 1984; MS023.006.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Equipment/supplies, 1983; MS023.006.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - [Financial statements], 1982 -- 1983; MS023.006.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Year end Goldstein statement, 1983; MS023.006.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - [Financial statements], 1985; MS023.006.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - [Financial statements], 1986 -- 1987; MS023.006.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - [Financial-FY 82, 990 for 85], 1982 -- 1985; MS023.006.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - FY 84 Adjustments, 1984; MS023.006.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - FY 85, 86 and 990, 1985 -- 1986; MS023.006.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Finance-misc., 1983; MS023.006.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - TheaterWorks [Finance misc.], 1983; MS023.006.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - [Financial-misc. budgeting], 1983 -- 1984; MS023.006.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Henry [Financial-misc.], 1983; MS023.006.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - [Outside professional services], 1985; MS023.006.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Prudential-Bache, 1984; MS023.006.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - [Receipts bundle], 1984; MS023.006.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - Visa/master card, 1983; MS023.006.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - Cash receipts journal, 1983 -- 1984; MS023.006.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - Mailing lists [Financial receipts], 1983 -- 1984; MS023.006.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - [Receipts and deposit slips], 1984 -- 1985; MS023.006.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - [Receipt-Misc.], 1986; MS023.006.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - January 1986-completed receipts forms [Reimbursement forms], MS023.006.006.00036 (Box 6)
  - February 1986-completed reimbursement forms, MS023.006.006.00037 (Box 6)
  - 1985 1099 and W2 copies, MS023.006.006.00038 (Box 6)
  - TheaterWorks 1099's, 1986; MS023.006.006.00039 (Box 6)
  - Tax exempt #, 1980 -- 1993; MS023.006.006.00040 (Box 6)
  - [Tax exempt application], 1980; MS023.006.006.00041 (Box 6)
  - Tax ex. forms, 1983 -- 1984; MS023.006.006.00042 (Box 6)
  - Federal taxes, 1984 -- 1986; MS023.006.006.00043 (Box 6)
  - Tax-federal (IRS), 1980 -- 1983; MS023.006.006.00044 (Box 6)
  - [Taxes, IRS 990], 1983 -- 1984; MS023.006.006.00045 (Box 6)
  - [Taxes, IRS 990], 1985 -- 1986; MS023.006.006.00046 (Box 6)
  - Taxes-state, 1983; MS023.006.006.00047 (Box 6)